justadventure.com 2017-12-21

# Just Adventure, LLC.

Just Adventure LLC. (hereafter called “Just Adventure”) is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its products and services and of individuals visiting our websites. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure Internet environment for consumers. 

All references in this policy to "Just Adventure " include the Just Adventure Network sites. The purpose of this Just Adventure privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Just Adventure,

(1) What kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Just Adventure;

(2) how we may use that information;

(3) whether we disclose it to anyone; and

(4) the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Just Adventure  and Web sites that carry the Just Adventure  brand, and not to other companies or organizations’ Web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked Just Adventure  and these branded Web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies. 

Just Adventure welcomes comments and questions on this policy. Just Adventure is dedicated to protecting your personal information. Due to the rapidly evolving nature of the technologies Just Adventure uses to communicate with you, we may occasionally update this policy. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this site. 

Just Adventure collects personally identifying information during:

(i) tournament, contest or sweepstakes registration;

(ii) subscription registration; and

(iii) registration for certain interactive areas on Just Adventure  and on Web sites that carry the Just Adventure brand, where visitors also provide content submissions and suggestions or participate in interactive online activities (i.e., community postings, voting, chat, or forums, bulletin boards, mailing lists). 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes and we collect that visitor’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible). In addition, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, forums, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information about which pages visitors access, user-specific information about which pages visitors access, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or information provided in site registration forms, including but not limited to a visitor’s name, address, and phone number. If a visitor signs up for a pay service, we also collect credit card information along with a billing address. Just Adventure may retain personally identifying information indefinitely. 

Just Adventure maintains publicly available user profiles as well, which may contain personally identifying information volunteered by its visitors. 

Just Adventure may use personally identifying information of its visitors to award prizes, track compliance with our Rules of Conduct, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when visitors provide the information). 

In addition, Just Adventure may disclose personally identifying information when Just Adventure believes in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Just Adventure. 

When a visitor creates a user profile or participates in public areas, including voice chat areas, all information volunteered is displayed or broadcast publicly to the Just Adventure community. Visitors should keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - in a user profile or in chat areas, for example - that information can be collected and used by others who visit that public area. In addition, Just Adventure may record audio conversations that take place in public chat rooms on our site for use in promoting our company or its services. We will not, however, record audio conversations that occur in locked chat rooms. 

Other companies which provide services on our site, or which advertise on our site, may collect information about you. Just Adventure does not control collection or use of this information. You should contact these companies or advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of this information. We will provide notice to you if one of our partners or sponsors collects information about you on our site, such as through a tournament, sweepstake, or contest. 

With the permission of a visitor who is 18 years of age or over, information submitted at the time of registration or submission - including but not limited to age, phone number, address, and income level - may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Just Adventure  and may be shared with companies that have been pre-screened by Just Adventure . If a visitor objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use— by sending an email to [general@justadventure.com](mailto:general@justadventure.com)

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, you can unsubscribe by sending an e-mail with your exact name and address general@justadventure.com

We also will notify other organizations with whom we share such information and request that they remove your information from their mailing lists. 

with confidence. We have partnered with Bank Card Services, PayPal, Google and Amazon to offer you the best and safe, secure credit card and payment services

Just Adventure adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: 

128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. 

Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. 

Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard.

Whenever you give Just Adventure  sensitive information (credit card numbers, for instance), Just Adventure  will take commercially reasonable steps to establish a secure connection with your web browser. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes. 

**Policies for individuals under 18**

Just Adventure encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children (persons under the age of 18 years old) and to participate in the interactive activities offered on our service. No information should be submitted to or posted at Just Adventure web sites by visitors under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

We will not knowingly use information collected from visitors under 18 years of age for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Just Adventure.  Visitors’ e-mail addresses are not posted on our web site or sub sites, unless provided by a visitor as part of a user profile.

Just Adventure collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers—the big computers that "serve" up Web pages—automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

When visitors request pages from Just Adventure, our servers log their IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. This means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.

Use of Cookies - What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you’re at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard—you’ll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use the site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. If you accept the first tracking cookie from Just Adventure , you won’t be offered as many afterwards. 

A cookie lets our computers remember that you’ve registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. Our online store uses a temporary cookie to track which products you’ve chosen to purchase while shopping. The cookie expires once you’re done shopping. Letting it do the record keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again during a single visit. If you decline this cookie, you may have difficulty ordering your selections. 

Just Adventure does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except as described below, Just Adventure does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. Just Adventure does not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping (see above) and contest registration (where a cookie allows you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time).

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Just Adventure does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the Just Adventure cookies policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, like the shopping areas, will not function properly if you do so. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Just Adventure Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of Just Adventure following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

**Revised:** May 1, 2013
